<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide app</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    //Locations category
    <string name="category_land_marks">Land marks</string>
    <string name="category_museums">Museums</string>
    <string name="category_restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="category_hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="address_head">Address</string>

    // Land Marks Strings
    <string name="giza_necropolis">Giza Necropolis</string>
    <string name="cairo_tower">Cairo Tower</string>
    <string name="pyramid_of_djoser">Pyramid of Djoser</string>
    <string name="khan_elKhalili">Khan el-Khalili</string>
    <string name="mosque_of_muhammad_ali">Mosque of Muhammad Ali</string>
    <string name="cairo_citadel">Cairo Citadel</string>
    <string name="the_hanging_church">The Hanging Church</string>
    <string name="egyptian_museum">Egyptian Museum</string>

    // Land Marks Address Strings
    <string name="cairo_tower_address">Zamalek, Cairo Governorate</string>
    <string name="pyramid_of_djoser_address">Al Giza Desert, Giza Governorate</string>
    <string name="giza_necropolis_address">Al Haram, Giza Governorate</string>
    <string name="khan_elKhalili_address">El-Gamaleya, El Gamaliya, Cairo Governorate</string>
    <string name="mosque_of_muhammad_ali_address">Al Abageyah, El-Khalifa, Cairo Governorate</string>
    <string name="cairo_citadel_address">Al Abageyah, Qesm Al Khalifah، Cairo Governorate</string>
    <string name="the_hanging_church_address">Kom Ghorab, Old Cairo, Cairo Governorate</string>
    <string name="egyptian_museum_address">Tahrir Square rd Tahrir Square, Cairo Governorate</string>

    // Land Marks information Strings
    <string name="cairo_tower_information">The Cairo Tower is a free-standing concrete tower in Cairo,
        Egypt. At 187 m, it has been the tallest structure in Egypt and North Africa for about 50
        years. It was the tallest structure in Africa for ten years until 1971, when it was
        surpassed by Hillbrow Tower in South Africa.
    </string>
    <string name="pyramid_of_djoser_information">The Pyramid of Djoser, or Step Pyramid is an archeological
        remain in the Saqqara necropolis, Egypt, northwest of the city of Memphis. The 6-tier, 4-sided
        structure is the earliest colossal stone building in Egypt
    </string>
    <string name="giza_necropolis_information">The Giza pyramid complex, also called the Giza Necropolis,
        is the site on the Giza Plateau in Egypt that includes the Great Pyramid of Giza, the Pyramid
        of Khafre, and the Pyramid of Menkaure, along with their associated pyramid complexes and the
        Great Sphinx of Giza.
    </string>
    <string name="khan_elKhalili_information">Khan el-Khalili is a major souk in the historic center of
        Islamic Cairo. The bazaar district is one of Cairo\'s main attractions for tourists and Egyptians
        alike.
    </string>
    <string name="mosque_of_muhammad_ali_information">The Great Mosque of Muhammad Ali Pasha or Alabaster
        Mosque is a mosque situated in the Citadel of Cairo in Egypt and was commissioned by Muhammad Ali
        Pasha between 1830 and 1848.
    </string>
    <string name="cairo_citadel_information">The Citadel of Cairo or Citadel of Saladin is a medieval
        Islamic-era fortification in Cairo, Egypt, built by Salah ad-Din and further developed by
        subsequent Egyptian rulers. It was the seat of government in Egypt and the residence of its
        rulers for nearly 700 years from the 13th to the 19th centuries.
    </string>
    <string name="the_hanging_church_information">Saint Virgin Mary\'s Coptic Orthodox Church, also known
        as The Hanging Church is one of the oldest churches in Egypt and the history of a church on this
        site dates to the third century. It belongs to the Coptic Orthodox Church of Alexandria.
    </string>
    <string name="egyptian_museum_information">    The Museum of Egyptian Antiquities, known commonly as
        the Egyptian Museum or Museum of Cairo, in Cairo, Egypt, is home to an extensive collection of
        ancient Egyptian antiquities. It has 120,000 items, with a representative amount on display,
        the remainder in storerooms.
    </string>

    //Museum Strings
    <string name="museum_of_islamic_art">Museum of Islamic Art</string>
    <string name="museum_of_islamic_art_address">Port Said, St، El-Darb El-Ahmar, Cairo Governorate</string>
    <string name="museum_of_islamic_art_info">The Museum of Islamic Art in Cairo, Egypt is considered
        one of the greatest in the world, with its exceptional collection of rare woodwork and plaster
        artefacts, as well as metal, ceramic, glass, crystal, and textile objects of all periods, from
        all over the Islamic world
    </string>











</resources>
